## NATHALIE PETTERSSON

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER



0739693669

nathalie.pettersson90@gmail.com

nathaliepettersson.se

www.linkedin.com/in/nathaliedeveloper/

### **PROFILE**

I would like to be a part of a team and come together to find creative solutions and drive technology forward. I believe the key to good results is open communication, and a team composed of different experiences, backgrounds and skills. I take on most challenges in a methodical and calm way with a high doze of patience.

## SKILLS

**REACT** 

JAVASCRIPT/TYPESCRIPT

HTML/CSS

COMMUNICATION

**LEADERSHIP** 

GIT

**SCRUM** 

**SVELTE** 

**CYPRESS** 

**DATABASEHANDLING** 

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER, INTERNSHIP

Extrapreneur AB Feb 2023 - April 2023

- Built an e-commerce site with React for Frontend and C# for
  Backend as a part of a traineeprogram along with other students
- Planned our work using Scrum methods and Jira as a tool

#### FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER, INTERNSHIP

Coolstuff AB

Nov 2022 - Feb 2023

- Improved their e-commerce site developed in Svelte and TypeScript
- Attended both planning and evaluation of the work together with the team
- Close dialogue and teamwork with senior developers who also shared knowledge and gave helpful feedback

## EDUCATION

#### FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

Grit Academy

Aug 2021 - Jun 2023

https://gritacademy.se/front-endwebbutvecklare/

# ENGLISH FOR PROFESSIONAL PURPOSES

Malmö University

Jan 2021 - Jun 2021

#### MANAGER WAREHOUSE

Apotek 1 Gruppen AS 2016 - 2021

- Held meetings and lead a team of warehouse workers on a daily basis
- According to my supervisors, I contributed with work satisfaction among the employees and helped increase productivity
- Handled unexpected situations in the best possible way by being flexible and helping to motivate every individual's work

#### WAREHOUSE WORKER

2013 - 2016